https://www.mgwshifters.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
0 items in your cart.
Our Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are
concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is
being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information
security, is information that can be used on its own or with other
information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to
identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy
carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect
or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in
accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that
visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be
asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number,
credit card information or other details to help you with your
experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an
order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form
or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make
a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or
marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site
features in the following ways:
To personalize
user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and
product offerings in which you are most interested.
To improve our
website in order to better serve you.
To allow us to
better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly
process your transactions.
To send periodic
emails regarding your order or other products and services.
How do we protect visitor information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known
vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as
possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is
only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access
rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information
confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply
is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order
enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety
of your personal information.
For your convenience we may store your credit card information longer
than 60 days in order to expedite future orders, and to automate the
billing process.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider
transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if
you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to
recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items
in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your
preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables
us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help
us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so
that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
Help remember
and process the items in the shopping cart.
Understand and
save user's preferences for future visits.
Compile
aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to
offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use
trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is
being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this
through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each
browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu
to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If users disable cookies in their browser:
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn
off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient
and some of our services will not function properly.
However, you can still place orders
saved shopping cart, order history, creating/managing an account,
other features that may or may not negatively affect the user's
experience
over the telephone by contacting customer service.
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance
notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site
policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other
parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
We do not include or offer third party products or services on our
website.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's
Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive
experience for users.
https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We utilize Google's AdSense services to meet some of our online marketing needs. Some anonymous data that could be used to uniquely identify you may be transmitted and/or stored to Google's services. For more information on how Google utilizes anonymous data, please Google it!
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our
site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to
our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the
Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by
visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party
cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies
(such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers
together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad
impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our
website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using
the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by
visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or
permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial
websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach
stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the
United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites
collecting personally identifiable information from California
consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating
exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom
it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at:
http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our
home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering
our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily
be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
On our Privacy Policy Page
Users are able to change their personal information
By emailing us.
By calling us.
By logging in to their account on www.mgwshifters.com.
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use
advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking. This means that we do not allow any third party services, such as online marketing & advertising providers, to monitor and track how you use our website. We understand the value of your privacy; we have invested significant resources into protecting your data.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children
under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts
parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer
protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what
operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's
privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13, intentionally or otherwise.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy
law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a
significant role in the development of data protection laws around the
globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how
they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various
privacy laws that protect personal information.
We adhere to the Fair Information Practices. We encrypt your personal information using a combination of encryption algorithms to ensure that your information is kept safe and secure. Although highly unlikely, it is possible for an unauthorized person to gain access to the data stored in any of our databases. All sensitive information contained within any database is encrypted prior to being saved to the database making it practically impossible to read the data in plain text as it was originally entered into said database. In the event of a data breach, we will notify all users via email within seven (7) business days. We will also post a notification on the homepage of our website within seven (7) business days.
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email,
establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the
right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out
tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
We are 100% CANSPAM compliant! To be CANSPAM compliant, we agree to:
NOT use false or misleading subjects.
NOT use false or misleading email addresses as the sender of the email.
Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from MGW, you may do so by:
Following the instructions provided at the bottom of each email.
Calling us during normal business hours.
Sending an email to privacy@mgwshifters.com. Requests sent to privacy@mgwshifters.com may take up to 45 days to be removed.
Contacting Us
Your privacy is extremely important to us. If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at any time.
MGW LTD
4159 Mike Padgett Highway
Augusta, GA 30906
(706) 793-1770
privacy@mgwshifters.com
MGW currently manufactures the best short throw shifters for Camaros, Corvettes, and Mustangs. We design and manufacture all of our components in house and only sell direct to the customer, giving you the highest quality products for the best possible price.
MGW Ltd.
© 2020 MGW Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
Return Policy -
Privacy Policy -
Terms & Conditions
